{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "145", "optb": "245", "optc": "123", "optd": "234", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "124", "optb": "345", "optc": "123", "optd": "135", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "124", "optb": "125", "optc": "234", "optd": "245", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "124", "optc": "135", "optd": "145", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "134", "optb": "345", "optc": "234", "optd": "135", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "124", "optb": "234", "optc": "345", "optd": "235", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "135", "optb": "123", "optc": "145", "optd": "234", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "234", "optc": "345", "optd": "245", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "234", "optc": "134", "optd": "235", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "134", "optc": "135", "optd": "345", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "145", "optb": "234", "optc": "134", "optd": "235", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "145", "optb": "135", "optc": "235", "optd": "234", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "134", "optb": "124", "optc": "234", "optd": "345", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "235", "optc": "245", "optd": "145", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "145", "optb": "234", "optc": "245", "optd": "135", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "125", "optc": "234", "optd": "245", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "124", "optb": "234", "optc": "345", "optd": "235", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "124", "optc": "125", "optd": "235", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "125", "optb": "123", "optc": "235", "optd": "234", "ans": "A", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "134", "optc": "135", "optd": "145", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "234", "optc": "124", "optd": "245", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "134", "optc": "235", "optd": "345", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "234", "optc": "134", "optd": "345", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "134", "optb": "145", "optc": "125", "optd": "124", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "124", "optc": "134", "optd": "345", "ans": "C", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "123", "optb": "345", "optc": "245", "optd": "234", "ans": "D", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "Select the alternative which represents three out of the five alternative figures which when fitted into each other would form a complete square.", "opta": "124", "optb": "235", "optc": "134", "optd": "245", "ans": "B", "explanation": ""}]]}